import 'package:flutter/material.dart';

Color primaryBlack = Color(0xff202c3b);

class DataSource {
  //static String quote =
  //"Nothing in life is to be feared, it is only to be understood. Now is the time to understand more, so that we may fear less.";

  static List questionAnswers = [
    {
      "question": "What is your motive?",
      "answer":
          "We aim at delivering fresh, clean, healthy and chemical free groceries and food items at affordable cost. "
    },
    {
      "question": "Where do you get the groceries from?",
      "answer":
          "There are multiple trusted sources of the grocery items including farmers, retailers and ourselves. All these sorces are 100% hygenic, chemical free and trustworthy. The retailers all are licensed and we aim at their goodwill too"
    },
    {
      "question": "Do you clean the groceries before delivering?",
      "answer": "Of course we clean it and make sure it's even good to go raw."
    },
    {
      "question": "Why do you say that your products are chemical-free?",
      "answer":
          "The sources are 100% trustworthy and the farmers never usually use chemical fertilisers or pesticides. The transportation and packaging ensures that no external chemicals contaminate the product. "
    },
    {
      "question": "Are the fishes fresh and chemical-free too?",
      "answer":
          "We have observed a large percent of fish markets using ammonia to preserve fish for a long time. We never consult them upon any circumstances. Even of we are out of stock, we won't buy from those markets. We try to provide freshly caught fishes not older than a day."
    },
    {
      "question": "Do you ensure that the meats do not have hormones in them?",
      "answer":
          "We take great care to ensure that there are no growth promoters such as hormones or antibiotics in the meat that you buy from  us. "
    },
    {
      "question":
          "What will happen if we eat chicken with growth hormones injected?",
      "answer":
          "Short term consumption of hormones chicken won’t harm to our body but long term may adversely affect our health. For example esteogen hormones which is also called female hormones are given to the chicken feeds for early growth and proper development of breast meat. If the man consume those esteogens treated meat the estrogens will start deposit in our body. After long term use the estrogens will start show its effect on the male. They will developed breast, their voice become sharp like as women’s voice. They will loose their facial hairs, also the hips also get broaden. This is just a example of estrogen hormones and other hormones also show their own side effect."
    },
    {
      "question": "What are the payment options supported?",
      "answer":
          "Currently to ease our service, we are only limited to Cash On Delivery. If you insist in paying online, you can pay us via google pay."
    },
    {
      "question": "What measures have you taken to prevent the corona pandemic",
      "answer":
          "We try our best to maintain social distancing and use sanitizers and washes hands often. We wear masks so that others won't we won't becoem carriers of the virus. We follow every norms put forth by WHO and the government to overcome COVID19"
    },
    {
      "question": "Should I wear a mask to protect myself?",
      "answer":
          "Only wear a mask if you are ill with COVID-19 symptoms (especially coughing) or looking after someone who may have COVID-19. Disposable face mask can only be used once. If you are not ill or looking after someone who is ill then you are wasting a mask. There is a world-wide shortage of masks, so WHO urges people to use masks wisely.\nWHO advises rational use of medical masks to avoid unnecessary wastage of precious resources and mis-use of masks\nThe most effective ways to protect yourself and others against COVID-19 are to frequently clean your hands, cover your cough with the bend of elbow or tissue and maintain a distance of at least 1 meter (3 feet) from people who are coughing or sneezing"
    }
  ];
}
